<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on AInI</title>
    <link>https://ainizecm.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on AInI</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 May 2017 21:13:14 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ainizecm.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Avoiding or Hiding Tableau filters - Part I</title>
      <link>https://ainizecm.github.io/2017/05/avoiding-or-hiding-tableau-filters---part-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2017 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ainizecm.github.io/2017/05/avoiding-or-hiding-tableau-filters---part-i/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to Tableau Dashboards, I am known as a filter-hater within my team. I find them ugly and not very user friendly. That’s why I always try to find new ways to avoid, hide or just make filters more user-friendly.
It usually helps me going through the following process:
Built a Dashboard that is able to show the needed level of detail (use all the filters you need)See if some coloring/shaping can helpIf filtering is needed, can you incorporate it nicely in the view?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Avoiding or Hiding Tableau filters - Part II</title>
      <link>https://ainizecm.github.io/2017/05/avoiding-or-hiding-tableau-filters---part-ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2017 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ainizecm.github.io/2017/05/avoiding-or-hiding-tableau-filters---part-ii/</guid>
      <description>Following from the previous post on “Avoiding or Hiding Tableau filters - Part I”, let’s get down to the nitty gritty how tos!
We start with a graph and a filter, simple.
The following graph shows the percentage of people per state that agree with each of the statements. Each state is a bar, the more on the right the bar is the bigger percentage of the population in that specific state agrees with that sentence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>https://ainizecm.github.io/2017/05/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2017 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ainizecm.github.io/2017/05/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Hello world!
I am Ainize, Commercial Analyst in Global during the day and Consultant for ISGlobal at night. I am passionate about analytics, decision making, data, frameworks and having an impact through numbers. And that is what I will be writing about.
Bilbao, Utrecht, Barcelona, Chicago and London are how I would describe my career so far. Each city has given me something different and special, not only at a professional level.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>